# **AKINGBADE MOTOLANI**

+ 234(0) 815 246 8934 | akingbademotolani@yahoo.co.uk

## **PROFILE**

Insightful computer science graduate with expertise in python, web development, postman, cypress, SQL, Microsoft office, and Adobe software. I graduated from Olashore International School in 2018 and am set to graduate from Babcock University in July 2022. I am extremely interested in new technologies as well as the art of testing various technologies and applications. My primary emphasis in the technology arena is software testing and data analysis.

### **EDUCATION**

# **Babcock University**

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science [GPA: 3.9/5.0]

Ogun state, Nigeria

2018 - 2022

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

### Student Intern - Infranet Ltd.

Worked majorly in the IT and networking department, helping with office issues that are IT related and had various opportunities of working close to the managing director when he had to go inspect on site jobs ranging from telecommunications site to oil and gas

Lagos state, Nigeria Jan 2021–August 2021

# **Internship - Pixels Digital Systems**

Spent 3 months learning the art of photography and making using of different adobe packages. Covered various events as both lead and assisting photographer, also had the opportunity to have an insight about branding

Oyo state, Nigeria June 2018 - August 2018

# **CERTIFICATION AND PROJECTS**

- ISTQB Foundation certified tester
- Quales Consulting training
- Built a simple compiler
- Facial recognition for attendance system

# **SKILLS**

- Advanced Microsoft Excel
- HTML,SQL,Python
- Tableau, Postman, Cypress
- Adobe Photoshop, Lightroom, Dreamweaver
- Problem solving and critical thinking
- Marketing and communication